Have you fully healed from, you
know, what happened in Jersey
ジャージーで起きたこと
もう完全に癒えた？
where you got shot seven times?
7発も撃たれたやつ
Have you fully healed from that?
完全に回復したの？
Because that has to be a type of
trauma that it's like
あれってトラウマになるじゃん
you're continuously looking over
your shoulder.
ずっと背後を
警戒し続けるような
You're continuously making sure you
make the right moves.
常に正しく動けてるか
気を張ってるような
Have you healed?
回復した？
It's crazy, though. Like, today, day
and age,
それがヤバくてさ
最近になって
like, yeah, I be catching myself like,
oh, that PTSD done worn off.
「あれ、PTSD抜けてんじゃん」って
ふと気づく時があんのよ
It worn off already?
もう抜けたの？
Yeah, I ain't gonna lie, it got like a
lot better.
ああ、正直
だいぶ良くなったよ
It was bad, it was bad, you feel me?
It was bad, you feel me?
ひどかったよ、マジでひどかった
ほんとにひどかったんだよ
And like, it's like, it feels like a lot
better right now.
でも今は
だいぶ楽になった感じ
I'm like a lot more like, you know.
前よりずっと…わかるだろ
Did you do something for it?
Like therapy?
何かしたの？セラピーとか
I ain't do nothing. Like, I'm like kind
of like an introvert.
何もしてねぇよ
俺ってちょっと内向的だからさ
I ain't do physical therapy, I ain't do
mental therapy.
リハビリもしてねぇし
メンタルのセラピーもしてねぇ
I just got the f**k away from
everybody and just... figured it out.
とにかく全員から離れて
自分でどうにかしたんだよ
So you just isolated yourself. Yep.
じゃあ一人で引きこもってたんだ
ああ
You were by yourself the
whole time?
ずっと一人で？
Yeah, basically. Yeah.
まぁ、基本的にはな
Do you move differently now with
that situation happening?
あの件があってから
動き方は変わった？
Because that's a scary situation.
だって怖い状況じゃん
Most people don't live off of
one shot,
普通は1発でも
生き残れないのに
but the fact that you were hit seven
times is very serious.
7発も食らったって
相当ヤバいことだよ
And actually, you know what's
crazy, though?
てか実際、ヤバいのがさ
I actually might have been more.
実はもっと多かったかもしんねぇ
You know, in the hospital, they
say more.
病院じゃもっと多いって
言われてんのよ
The news headline, seven, and I just
let it rock.
ニュースの見出しは7発で
俺はそのままにしといた
I just left it at seven. I ain't f**king
with you on seven.
7発ってことにしといたけど
7発どころじゃねぇよ
How many times was it, though?
実際は何発だったの？
It was like eight, nine.
8発か9発くらい
But you know this? I got f**king mad
holes and s**t.
それにさ
体中マジで穴だらけなんだよ